{
  "quizInfo": {
    "Subject": "Advanced Systems Integration and Architecture",
    "Term": "Prefinals",
    "Title": "Enterprise Asset Management (EAM) Part 1",
    "LastModified": "20 November 2024",
    "Authors": [
      "Alexander Oro"
    ],
    "References": [
      "05 Handout 1"
    ]
  },
  "quizData": [
    {
      "question": "This focuses on managing, maintaining, inspecting, and repairing plants of business assets throughout its life cycle.",
      "answer": "SAP EAM",
      "choices": [
        "SAP EAM",
        "SAP HCM",
        "SAP ERP",
        "SAP CS"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 - 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "For this system, assets refer to the equipment, machinery, and facilities that an organization has.",
      "answer": "SAP EAM",
      "choices": [
        "SAP EAM",
        "SAP HCM",
        "SAP ERP",
        "SAP PS"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 - 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which benefit specifies the statement?<BR>By proactively managing maintenance, unexpected breakdowns are lessened, eventually increasing critical asset reliability.",
      "answer": "Increased Asset Reliability",
      "choices": [
        "Increased Asset Reliability",
        "Improved Efficiency",
        "Cost-Saving",
        "Compliance and Safety"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 - 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which benefit specifies the statement?<BR>This leads to reduced downtime, faster response time, and optimized resource utilization. Businesses can operate without worries as assets are in good condition.",
      "answer": "Improved Efficiency",
      "choices": [
        "Increased Asset Reliability",
        "Improved Efficiency",
        "Cost-Saving",
        "Compliance and Safety"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 - 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which benefit specifies the statement?<BR>Through better asset management, businesses can control maintenance expenses, minimize unnecessary parts inventory, and extend the lifespan of assets.",
      "answer": "Cost-Saving",
      "choices": [
        "Increased Asset Reliability",
        "Improved Efficiency",
        "Cost-Saving",
        "Compliance and Safety"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 - 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which benefit specifies the statement?<BR>The business can meet regulatory compliance requirements and ensure that safety standards are upheld.",
      "answer": "Compliance and Safety",
      "choices": [
        "Increased Asset Reliability",
        "Improved Efficiency",
        "Cost-Saving",
        "Compliance and Safety"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 - 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "This is an independent environment in the system.",
      "answer": "Client",
      "choices": [
        "Client",
        "Company Code",
        "Plant",
        "Storage Location"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 - 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "This is the smallest organizational unit where a legal set of books can be maintained.",
      "answer": "Company Code",
      "choices": [
        "Company Code",
        "Client",
        "Plant",
        "Maintenance Planning Plant"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 - 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "This is the operating area of a branch within the company. It can be a manufacturing, distribution, purchasing, or maintenance facility",
      "answer": "Plant",
      "choices": [
        "Plant",
        "Maintenance Plant",
        "Maintenance Planning Plant",
        "Plant Section"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 - 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "This is an organizational unit allowing differentiation between the various stocks of material in a plant.",
      "answer": "Storage Location",
      "choices": [
        "Storage Location",
        "Plant",
        "Work Center",
        "Plant Section"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 - 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is required to store spare parts.",
      "answer": "This statement is TRUE.",
      "choices": [
        "This statement is TRUE.",
        "This statement is FALSE."
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 - 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "This is the plant wherein the technical objects of a company are installed and has oriented organizational units such as Location, Plant Section, and Work Center.",
      "answer": "Maintenance Plant",
      "choices": [
        "Maintenance Plant",
        "Maintenance Planning Plant",
        "Plant",
        "Plant Section"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 - 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "This is the plant in which maintenance tasks are planned and prepared.",
      "answer": "Maintenance Planning Plant",
      "choices": [
        "Maintenance Planning Plant",
        "Maintenance Plant",
        "Plant",
        "Plant Section"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 - 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which are the two parts of the Location?",
      "answer": "building number and coordinates",
      "choices": [
        "building number and coordinates",
        "address and location number",
        "building number and location number",
        "coordinates and location number"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 - 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "This is responsibility for working assets.",
      "answer": "Plant Section",
      "choices": [
        "Plant Section",
        "Work Center",
        "Plant",
        "Storage Location"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 - 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "This is the process measures of plant maintenance.",
      "answer": "Work Center",
      "choices": [
        "Work Center",
        "Plant Section",
        "Plant",
        "Storage Location"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 - 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "The master data involved in this SAP are Functional Location, Equipment, and the Bill of Master.",
      "answer": "SAP EAM",
      "choices": [
        "SAP EAM",
        "SAP HCM",
        "SAP ERP",
        "SAP CS"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 - 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is a hierarchically organized structure representing the location, a technical system, a building, or a part of it where a maintenance measure is performed.",
      "answer": "Functional Location",
      "choices": [
        "Functional Location",
        "Storage Location",
        "Plant",
        "Plant Section"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 - 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Functional locations cannot be used to subdivide the objects into similar maintenance units.",
      "answer": "This statement is FALSE.",
      "choices": [
        "This statement is TRUE.",
        "This statement is FALSE."
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 - 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is a benefit of the functional location master data?",
      "answer": "Structural depiction of technical plant",
      "choices": [
        "Structural depiction of technical plant",
        "Administration of individual objects and data",
        "Data gathering and analysis for extended periods",
        "Object-oriented cost monitoring"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 - 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is a benefit of the functional location master data?",
      "answer": "Planning and performing maintenance tasks",
      "choices": [
        "Planning and performing maintenance tasks",
        "Structuring of objects",
        "Service parts planning in maintenance orders and maintenance task list",
        "Within the plant maintenance, BOMs are used if there are similar objects that can be maintained"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 - 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is a benefit of the functional location master data?",
      "answer": "Verification of maintenance tasks",
      "choices": [
        "Verification of maintenance tasks",
        "Administration of individual objects and data",
        "Data gathering and analysis for extended periods",
        "Structuring of objects"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 - 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is a benefit of the functional location master data?",
      "answer": "Data gathering for extended time",
      "choices": [
        "Data gathering for extended time",
        "Administration of individual objects and data",
        "Data gathering and analysis for extended periods",
        "Within the plant maintenance, BOMs are used if there are similar objects that can be maintained"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 - 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is a benefit of the functional location master data?",
      "answer": "Cost monitoring",
      "choices": [
        "Cost monitoring",
        "Administration of individual objects and data",
        "Service parts planning in maintenance orders and maintenance task list",
        "Object-oriented cost monitoring"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 - 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is a benefit of the functional location master data?",
      "answer": "Behavioral analysis of individual areas under different conditions",
      "choices": [
        "Behavioral analysis of individual areas under different conditions",
        "Administration of individual objects and data",
        "Service parts planning in maintenance orders and maintenance task list",
        "Object-oriented cost monitoring"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 - 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is the physical object for which maintenance tasks are planned and performed.",
      "answer": "equipment",
      "choices": [
        "equipment",
        "location",
        "budget",
        "people"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 - 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which examples include pumps, personal computers, circulation fans, and engines?",
      "answer": "equipment",
      "choices": [
        "equipment",
        "location",
        "budget",
        "people"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 - 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "These can be placed in functional locations.",
      "answer": "equipments",
      "choices": [
        "equipments",
        "locations",
        "budget",
        "people"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 - 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is an advantage of the equipment master data?",
      "answer": "Administration of individual objects and data",
      "choices": [
        "Administration of individual objects and data",
        "Structural depiction of technical plant",
        "Planning and performing maintenance tasks",
        "Data gathering for extended time"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 - 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is an advantage of the equipment master data?",
      "answer": "Verification of maintenance tasks",
      "choices": [
        "Verification of maintenance tasks",
        "Cost monitoring",
        "Behavioral analysis of individual areas under different conditions",
        "Service parts planning in maintenance orders and maintenance task list"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 - 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is an advantage of the equipment master data?",
      "answer": "Object-oriented cost monitoring",
      "choices": [
        "Object-oriented cost monitoring",
        "Cost monitoring",
        "Behavioral analysis of individual areas under different conditions",
        "Structural depiction of technical plant"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 - 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is an advantage of the equipment master data?",
      "answer": "Data gathering and analysis for extended periods",
      "choices": [
        "Data gathering and analysis for extended periods",
        "Structural depiction of technical plant",
        "Planning and performing maintenance tasks",
        "Behavioral analysis of individual areas under different conditions"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 - 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is the complete structured list of all components.",
      "answer": "Bill of Material",
      "choices": [
        "Bill of Material",
        "Bill of Gates",
        "Bill y Eilish",
        "Bill of Master Data"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 - 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "It can be allocated to functional locations or equipment.",
      "answer": "Bill of Material",
      "choices": [
        "Bill of Material",
        "Bill of Gates",
        "Bill y Crawford",
        "Bill of Master Data"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 - 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "In EAM, it includes three (3) types of Bill of Material: Material BOMs, Equipment BOMs, and Function location BOMs.",
      "answer": "This statement is TRUE.",
      "choices": [
        "This statement is TRUE.",
        "This statement is FALSE."
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 - 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is an advantage of the BOM master data?",
      "answer": "Structuring of objects",
      "choices": [
        "Structuring of objects",
        "Verification of maintenance tasks",
        "Object-oriented cost monitoring",
        "Data gathering and analysis for extended periods"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 - 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is an advantage of the BOM master data?",
      "answer": "Service parts planning in maintenance orders and maintenance task list",
      "choices": [
        "Service parts planning in maintenance orders and maintenance task list",
        "Structural depiction of technical plant",
        "Planning and performing maintenance tasks",
        "Data gathering for extended time"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 - 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is an advantage of the BOM master data?",
      "answer": "Within the plant maintenance, BOMs are used if there are similar objects that can be maintained",
      "choices": [
        "Within the plant maintenance, BOMs are used if there are similar objects that can be maintained",
        "Object-oriented cost monitoring",
        "Verification of maintenance tasks",
        "Cost monitoring"
      ],
      "reference": "05 Handout 1 - 1",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    }
  ]
}
